# Andrius Mozūraitis, Full Stack NodeJS Developer

andriusmozuraitis@gmail.com | +37060262684 https://github.com/digimuza

**SUMMARY** 

I'm a full stack web developer who can build apps from the ground up. I've worked mostly at startups so I am use to wearing many hats. I am a very product focussed developer who priotizes user feedback first and foremost. I'm generally very flexible when investigating new roles.

**EXPERIENCE** 

#### SearchNode, Fullstack NodeJS Developer

2018-05-05 — Present

https://searchnode.com/

- Searchnode provides excellent search experience for ecommerce platform.
- Worked with huge amounts of data
- PRO level on Typescript
- Product development
- o Node.js inside out
- o Developed 12 libraries each are designed for agile development

#### Passcamp, Fullstack NodeJS Developer

2016-03-01 — 2018-01-01

https://www.passcamp.com/

- Password manager for teams that protects the privacy and safety of your company's data.
- o Developed SPA using Angular 4+
- Developed backend using GoLang / NodeJS
- Chrome / Safari extension development
- o Docker / GCP
- Used Figma for design and UX work
- Mastered SQL using Postgres database

## AdeoWeb, Fullstack NodeJS Developer

2014-10-01 — 2016-03-01

https://www.adeoweb.lt/

- o Wordpress developer
- o Developed Wordpress websites
- Plugins for wordpress

**EDUCATION** 

### Kaunas university of applied sciences

2008-02-12 — 2009-12-12

Bachelors - Software Engineering (incomplete)

SKILLS

**Frontend** (*Senior*): HTML / JSX, SCSS / CSS, Javascript / Typescript, React / Next, AngularJS **Backend** (*Senior*): Node, Python, Postgres, Redis, Serverless, Mongo, Firebase, Elastic **Devops** (*Senior*): AWS, G Cloud, Heroku, Jenkins, Docker, Kubernetes

LANGUAGES

English (B1), Lithuania (Native speaker)

INTERESTS

Toastmasters, Music / Jamming, Reading / Writing, Open Source